{"questions":[
	{"qid":101,"question":"What color are zebras?","optionA":"White with black stripes","optionB":"Black with white stripes","optionC":"Both of the above","optionD":"None of the above","answer":"optionA"},	
	{"qid":102,"question":"Which of the following dog breeds is the smallest?","optionA":"Dachshund","optionB":"Poodle","optionC":"Pomeranian","optionD":"Chihuahua","answer":"optionD"},
	{"qid":103,"question":"What is the fastest water animal?","optionA":"Porpoise","optionB":"Sailfish","optionC":"Flying fish","optionD":"Tuna","answer":"optionB"},
	{"qid":104,"question":"Which of the following animals sleeps standing up?","optionA":"Gorillas","optionB":"Flamingos","optionC":"Hedgehogs","optionD":"Ravens","answer":"optionB"},
	{"qid":105,"question":"What is the capital of England?","optionA":"Tokyo","optionB":"Paris","optionC":"London","optionD":"Rio de Janeiro","answer":"optionC"},
	{"qid":106,"question":"What are some things you can do to help support your brain health?","optionA":"Eating nutritious foods","optionB":"Regular physical activity","optionC":"Doing mental exercises like crossword puzzles and other games","optionD":"All of the above","answer":"optionD"},
	{"qid":107,"question":"The great Victoria Desert is located in?","optionA":"Canada","optionB":"West Africa","optionC":"Australia","optionD":"North America","answer":"optionC"},
	{"qid":108,"question":"The Homolographic projection has the correct representation of?","optionA":"shape","optionB":"area","optionC":"baring","optionD":"distance","answer":"optionB"},
	{"qid":109,"question":"The longest ship canal in the world is the?","optionA":"St. Laurence Seaway (USA and Canada)","optionB":"Suez canal, Egypt","optionC":"Kiel canal, Germany","optionD":"Panama canal, Central America","answer":"optionA"},
	{"qid":110,"question":"The meridian passing through London is called the?","optionA":"equator","optionB":"Tropic of Cancer","optionC":"Prime Meridian of 0 Meridian","optionD":"Tropic of Capricorn","answer":"optionC"}
]}